https://cartamundi.com/en/privacy/

Cartamundi - Privacy & Cookies
Cartamundi
HomeServicesOur BrandsCasesAboutOur storyOur locationsCorporate GovernanceContactJobsTechnicalPress Area
Search
InternationalenNLFR
Search for:
X
Visit cartamundi.comOr choose your countryBelgiumCartamundi – Digital NVBelgiumCartamundi – HeadquartersBrazilFranceGermanyKönigsfurt Urania Verlag GmbHGermanyASS/ Spielkartenfabrik Altenburg GmbHHungaryIndiaIrelandItalyJapanNetherlandsPolandSingaporeSpainNaipes Heraclio Fournier, S.A.SpainCartamundi España, S.L.SwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomNorth AmericaThe United States Playing Card CompanyNorth AmericaCartamundi North America East Longmeadow LLCSearch
Search for:
Privacy & Cookies
PrivacyPersonal DataIn this Privacy Statement we refer to Cartamundi Services NV, registered under company registration number 0877.568.403, and Cartamundi Turnhout NV, registered under company registration number 0877.566.324 (jointly referred to as “Cartamundi”). There are various purposes for which Cartamundi may use the personal or business data you provide.Please read our Privacy statement for more information on the use of your data.COOKIESCartamundi uses cookies to simplify your browsing experience on the Cartamundi Website and make it more enjoyable. Cookies also enable us to adjust the content of our website to better suit your needs and preferences.It is possible to set your browser to refuse the installation of cookies, but this may adversely affect the performance of some parts of the Cartamundi Website. By continuing to browse the Cartamundi Website without changing your cookie settings and by clicking “OK”, we assume that you accept the installation of our cookies.Please read our Cookie statement for more information on the use of cookies.Your rightsIf you have a complaint regarding our processing of your personal data, you can always contact us using the contactform. If you are still not satisfied with our answer, then you are at liberty to file a complain with the competent data protection authority, the Belgian Privacy Commission. For more information.Cartamundi places a great deal of importance on protecting your privacy and personal data.
